A Finding Aid to the Jimmy Hedges Papers and Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery Records, 1969-2016, bulk 1991-2013, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, circa 1990-2011; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 7.9 Linear feet Boxes 16-30, 34-35; 7.79 Gigabytes ER20-ER35
  - Artists and Artwork, circa 1990-2011; 8.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Judith Racht, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20-21)
    - Sarah Rakes, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - William Rhodes, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Royal Robertson, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Simone Robinson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Marie Rogers, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 26-29)
    - Max Romain, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 30-35)
    - Schlachter, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Milton Schwartz, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - J.P. Scott, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Jon Serl, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 39-40)
    - Welmond Sherborne, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Charles Simmons, circa 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 42-68)
    - Charles Simmons, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1-8)
    - Earl Simmons, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9-14)
    - Bernice Sims, circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
    - Issac Smith, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17-19)
    - Lucile Smith, circa 1992-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20-22)
    - Mary T. Smith, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Stephanie Smither, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Charlie Stagg, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25-28)
    - Joe Storm, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Sterling Strauser, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Sterling and Dot Strauser, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 31-32)
    - Vannoy Strather, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - David Strickland, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Jimmy Lee Sudduth, circa 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 35-60)
    - Jimmy Lee Sudduth, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1-21)
    - Rev. Johnnie Swearingen, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 22-24)
    - Sarah Mary Taylor, circa 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 25-33)
    - Pop Thayer, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 34-35)
    - James "Son Ford" Thomas, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 36-39)
    - Annie Tolliver, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 40-41)
    - Annie and Mose "Mose T" Tolliver, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 42-46)
    - Annie, Charles, and Mose "Mose T" Tolliver, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Annie, Charles, Jimmy, and Mose "Mose T" Tolliver, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Jimmy Tolliver, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Mose "Mose T" Tolliver, circa 1992-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 50-53)
    - Control Valdez, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 54-55)
    - Ron Vanbike, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Rev. Albert Wagoner, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 57-60)
    - Hubert Walters, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Hubert Walters, circa 1995-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER23 (Box 25, Folder 1-7)
    - Hubert Walters, Digital Photographs, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.053 Gigabytes 23 computer files (Folder ER23)
    - Derek Webster, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Mr. Welters, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Myrtice West, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 10-12)
    - Bobby Whalen, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Willie White, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 14-15)
    - Knox Wilkinson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
    - Delelle Williams, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Ruby Williams, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Allen Wilson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 20-21)
    - Charles Worley, circa 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 22-24)
    - Survivor Interviews - Charley Worley, Digital Video Recording, 2012; Archival Resource Key; 0.113 Gigabytes Two computer files (Folder ER24)
    - Purvis Young, circa 1991-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 25-36)
    - Purvis Young, circa 1990-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 1-36)
    - Purvis Young, circa 1990-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 1-52)
    - Malka Zeldis, circa 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 37-38)
    - Photograph Album, Leroy Almon and Myrtice West, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 39-40)
    - Bill Arnett and A.J. Mohammed, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Homer Green and J.L. Nipper, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 42-43)
    - Photograph Album, Lonnie Holley, Howard Finster, and Leroy Alman, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Lonnie Holley and Homer Green, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Photograph Album, A.J. Mohammed and Loy Bowlin "Rhinestone Cowboy", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Photograph Album, Earl Simmons, James "Son Ford" Thomas, and Luster Willis, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 47-49)
    - Annie Tolliver and Purvis Young, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Ernest Williams and Charlie Stagg, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Purvis Young and Jimmy Lee Sudduth, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Photograph Album of Artists (Dismantled), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 53-58)
    - Photograph Album of Artists (Dismantled), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Photograph Album, "Artist Photos" (Dismantled), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 2-7)
    - Photograph Album of Artwork (Dismantled), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 8-19)
    - Photograph Album of Artwork 2 (Dismantled), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 20-23)
    - African American Furniture, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Angel Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - "Art in my House", 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Belzoni Sign, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Micki Beths Collection, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Bird Houses, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Bottle Tree, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - "Cane Man" - Sommerville, GA, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Cemetary Art, circa 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 31-37)
    - Dot's Place - Mississippi Stick Paintings, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Driftwood Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Electric Chair, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Face Jugs and Pottery, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Farm Dogs Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Furniture and Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Gallery Art, circa 1993-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1-15)
    - Kurt Gitter Collection, circa 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 16-22)
    - "Guns on my Mind", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Menek Office Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Quilts, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 25-28)
    - River Baptism Photo Series, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Stone Garden Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Wood Carvings and Guitars, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified Art, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 32-72)
    - Unidentified Art (Negatives), Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 73-76)
    - Miscellaneous Large Format Photographs, circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Slides of Artists and Artwork, circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
  - Events, circa 1992-2011; 8.2; Archival Resource Key
    - Art Box Opening, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - Art Car Parade, 2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital materials, see ER25 (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - Art Car Parade, Digital Photographs, 2010; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Gigabytes 244 computer files (Folder ER25)
    - Art Chicago/Intuit, circa 1997-2008; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital materials, see ER26 (Box 27, Folder 79-84)
    - Art Chicago/Intuit, Digital Photographs, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.057 Gigabytes 27 computer files (Folder ER26)
    - ARTS Exhibit, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 85)
    - Chicago Inside Show, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 86)
    - Finster Festival, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 87-88)
    - Folk Art Society Meeting Houston, TX, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 89)
    - Folk Art Society Meeting Washington, DC, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Folk Art South: Atlanta Annual Meeting, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Folk Fest, circa 1995-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER27-ER28 (Box 28, Folder 3-17)
    - Folk Fest, Digital Photographs, 2010; Archival Resource Key; 3.96 Gigabytes 226 computer files (Folder ER27)
    - Folk Fest, Digital Photographs, 2011; Archival Resource Key; 0.323 Gigabytes 180 computer files (Folder ER28)
    - Harbert Art Show, 1996-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 18-23)
    - Inside Outside, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Kimball Sterling Events, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 25-29)
    - Normal Palooza, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 30-31)
    - Outsider Art Fair, circa 1996-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital material, see ER29-ER30 (Box 28, Folder 32-47)
    - Outsider Art Fair, Digital Photographs, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.058 Gigabytes 26 computer files (Folder ER29)
    - Outsider Art Fair, Digital Photographs, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.249 Gigabytes 118 computer files (Folder ER30)
    - Outsiders Inside, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Piers Show NY, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Who-Fest, 2008; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital materials, see ER31 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Who-Fest, Digital Photographs, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.081 Gigabytes 34 computer files (Folder ER31)
    - Unidentified Art Shows, circa 1992-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 51-65)
    - Unidentified Art Shows, Digital Photographs, 2004-2011; Archival Resource Key; 1.28 Gigabytes 670 computer files (Folder ER32)
    - Unidentified Artist, Stainless Steel Box, Digital Photographs, 2003; Archival Resource Key; 0.005 Gigabytes Three computer files (Folder ER33)
  - Travel and Personal, circa 1991-2010; 8.3; Archival Resource Key
    - Alabama, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 66)
    - Atlanta, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 67)
    - Ava Maria Grotto, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 68)
    - Ava Maria Grotto, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Brickyard Rd., N.C. Artist, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Brimfield Wood Carver, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - California Trip, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Collinsville, AL, 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
    - Columbus, OH Artist, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - David Newele Performance, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - The Delta, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Finster's Art Studio, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Florida, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 11-13)
    - Folk Art Museum, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Folk Life Wall, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Gallery Christmas Card, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Gallery and Farm, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Hiking, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Kansas Concrete Park, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Kentucky Artists, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Lookout Mt., 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Lookout Mt./Chattanooga, undated; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital materials, see ER34 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Lookout Mt./Chattanooga, Digital Photographs, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.064 Gigabytes 27 computer files (Folder ER34)
    - Los Angeles Bottle Village, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Metro Arts Center Gallery, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 24-25)
    - Miami, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 26-28)
    - Mississippi, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 29-32)
    - Nashville Flea Market, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - New York Trip, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Personal - Hedges Family, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 35-39)
    - Personal - "Jimmy Painting", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Personal -"Portrait", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Personal - Miscellaneous, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Savannah Visit/Tybee Folk Artist, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Springfield, OH, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 45-46)
    - Stowe, Vermont Metal Sculptor, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Summerville, GA Trade Day, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 48-49)
    - Tennessee, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 50-51)
    - Texas Trips, 1994-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 52-57)
    - Variety Novelty Garden, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Voodoo Village Memphis, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Washington, DC, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Watts Tower Art Center, Los Angeles, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 61-63)
    - White House of the Confederacy, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Unidentified Negatives, circa 1990-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 65-67)
    - Unidentified Negatives, circa 1990-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 1-7)
    - Unidentified, Digital Photographs, 2000-2013; Archival Resource Key; 1.02 Gigabytes 1021 computer files (Folder ER35)
- Unidentified Sound and Video Recordings, undated; Series 9; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Boxes 30-31
  Found here are five unidentified VHS video recordings, as well as one identified sound cassette.
  - Unidentified Video Recordings, undated; Archival Resource Key; 4 Videocassettes (VHS); 1 Videocassettes (Hi8) This was found in the camcorder from the donor (Box 31)
  - Unidentified Video Recording, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS-C) (Box 30)
  - Unidentified Sound Recordings and Digital Sound Recordings, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette; 2 Sound discs (CD) (Box 30)